Ohh I really need to know
哦，我真的需要知道
Ohh Ya gotta let me go
哦，你将让我走开
This time I really need to do things right
这次我必须正确的做好这件事情
Shivers that ya give me keep me freezing all night
战栗，为你让我整晚感到自己像是冻僵了一样
Shudder
颤栗
I can't believe it, I'm not myself
我不能相信，我不是我自己
suddenly I'm thinkin' of no one else
突然我不去想任何人
You make me shudder
你让我颤栗
Ohh I really need to know
哦，我真的需要知道
(Or else you) gotta let me go
否则就让我离去
Your just a fantasy girl
你是一个梦幻般的女孩
In seven parts of the world
在世界的七个大洲
All I want is to be with you always
我所想要的只是与你一直在一起
I'll give you everything
我将给你一切
Give some attention to me
留给我一些关注
All I want is you and me always
我想要的是你我一直在一起
Give me affection
给我你的爱慕之情
I need your perfection
我需要你的完美
You feel so good
你让我感到如此之好
You make me stutter, stutter
你让我口吃，口吃
If I could touch you, I'd never let go
如果我可以碰触到你，我将永远不会放手
Now ya got me screaming and I cannot shut up, shut up
现在你让我尖叫，我难以停止，停止
Now I am lying on the bedroom floor barely even speaking
现在我躺在卧室地板上，甚至说话都感到困难
and I cannot get up, get up
我不能起来，起来
Ohh I really, I really, I really need to know
哦我真的，真的，我真的需要知道
Ya gotta let me go
你让我离开
Your just a fantasy girl
你是一个梦幻般的女孩
In seven parts of the world
在世界的七个大洲
All I want is to be with you always
我所想要的只是与你一直在一起
I'll give you everything
我将给你一切
Give some attention to me
留给我一些关注
All I want is you and me always
我想要的是你我一直在一起
Give me affection
给我你的爱慕之情
I need your perfection
我需要你的完美
You feel so good
你让我感到如此之好
You make me stutter, stutter
你让我口吃，口吃
You knock me down, I can't get up, I'm stuck
你让我失望，我不能起来，我被困住了
Gotta stop shaking me up
停止吧，让我振作
I cant eat, cant sleep, can't think, .....
我饭不思，夜不寐，不能思考……
Your just a fantasy girl
你是一个梦幻般的女孩
In seven parts of the world
在世界的七个大洲
All I want is to be with you always
我所想要的只是与你一直在一起
I'll give you everything
我将给你一切
Give some attention to me
留给我一些关注
All I want is you and me always
我想要的是你我一直在一起
Give your attention
留给我一些关注
I need your perfection
我需要你的完美
You feel so good
你让我感到如此之好
You make me stutter
你让我口吃
怎么唱？
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
非常好！
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
你们可以更大声的！
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
大家一起（唱）
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
再来一次
You make me shutter
你让我口吃
我需要你们全部人
每个人 都站起来
我要更多人  快点（站起来）
要听下一首吗   还要再听另外一首歌吗？
知道这首吗？跟着我们一起唱